so girls what do you think about this new face of mine be honest pretty hideous isn't it pretty
sad isn't it pretty ironic isn't it my wish was to ruin Iona's career but the only thing that got
ruined was my face it was my intention to end her modeling career but it happened to me instead
freaking insane isn't it come on it's funny isn't it you should be laughing
so
this is all your fault
what I lost to you and now I'm all alone with this jacked up face let's fix that you and you and Iona
I'm gonna carve all your faces up so you look just like me what are you kids doing here
hold up stay right there you two
Ruko let's book it
she kept her memories
uh yeah
then we're good
no we're not this is awful
Aki was right about the stuff she said
her wish getting corrupted is my fault
Ruko
look you still don't have a wish you should quit now while you're ahead
what
really if something bad happens think about what it would do to your grandma
the same thing goes for you too Yuzuki think about how your parents would feel if something
happened to you
and Kazuki he'd be heartbroken wouldn't he
I can't quit
you have to
come on you saw what losing did to Akira
I won't end up like her
yeah but you don't know that
Ruko it's sweet of you to worry
it is
no please
I have to keep pushing just a little more
I've come way too far to give up on my dream now
and I'm this close to making it happen
so
god I hate this
we can't be friends anymore
no matter what I'm going to be an eternal girl
if you keep hanging around with me
our friendship could be used against you and I don't want you to suffer
no wait
I'm sorry
Yuzuki please don't go
Ruko
it was really fun being your friend
our matching scrunchies I will treasure that forever
then why
next time we meet I'll be a new me
no more regrets
I'll finally be Kazuki's girlfriend for real
Devon
it's
little
the
that
's
which
they
the
like
you
hey
so
that more faced with comical feeling
until I need to have so many time
Divided on my way
Your name may depart, peronde it will fall
Let's try out what you want, what not
every world has yet to be left
My buyer's self riddle will not be GEORGIA
I will not be aware
乾いた後悔の海を飲み干す君は 限られた言葉でいつしかの笑顔 許して欲しいんだろう
現実を忘れたって構わないよ だから今も知らないでいたいのね
Hey
Ruko, call home if you're going to be late.
And where in the world have you been all this time anyway?
None of your business.
Fine, so it's not my business or whatever.
But still, you shouldn't worry Grandma like that.
It's not cool.
You okay?
Is she... is she home?
Yeah, go let her know you're alright.
Hi. Sorry.
Oh, thank goodness you're home.
Cold, cold, go away.
Lucky for you I made some hot cider.
I had a feeling you'd be cold after walking outside for so long.
Don't just stand there.
Grandma, why aren't you asking me questions about where I've been?
Because, dear, I know when you're ready to talk, you'll let me know.
Sound good to you?
and this is where I'm waiting for you.
Meow.
워.
Hey, Siammi?
Are you asleep?
I wish you were awake and having a battle,
because I like seeing how much fun you have!
But you know...
There's one thing that I don't like...
Seeing you sad...
Morning, Kazuki!
Woah, you made this?
Yep, sure did!
And by some miracle, I didn't even burn down the house!
Here, I made soup, too!
Thank goodness!
For soup?
Know that you finally came out of your room after last night.
I worried about you.
Girls have days like that,
so the best thing to do is steer clear and leave them be!
Yeah, say no more.
Good, now eat!
Right, and thanks for cooking!
It's good!
The last time you made French toast, it was a real disaster, remember?
Yeah, I used to rush things way too much.
Lose my cool and mess up.
No more of that, because I've learned to calm down.
Take my time and set my sights.
That way everything works out in the end, right?
I guess so.
Seen some friends?
Oh, yeah.
I won't be gone for too long.
Well, that's good.
Because I'm making dinner tonight.
Really?
I wonder what we should have.
We had French toast for breakfast, so for dinner…
Curry Udon!
Yeah, that's right, Kazuki.
I know you better than you know yourself.
Well, gotta jet.
Cool, have a good time.
Ito-e, I'm sorry, but I can't do it.
I can't lose and end up like you did.
I'm gonna make my wish come true.
Morning!
Hey, did you write that?
I'm not trying to get on your case, but isn't it kind of dangerous to find opponents like that?
Yeah, I don't know.
You're probably right.
Look, personally, I don't have a problem with it, but I could see where other selectors would.
Even my Elrig thinks it's kind of sketchy.
Well…
I can't wait for opponents to come find me.
I need to get this thing done already.
Huh?
Because I'm so close.
After I beat you, my wish will come true.
Wow, pretty confident, aren't you?
Alright then, let's do this.
Open!
Something tells me today's the day.
Huh?
I don't know what it is, but I feel different.
I think it's the end of the road.
Perhaps so.
Hario, get ready!
This girl is crazy, serious!
It's not wrong.
It never was.
I don't care what people think.
The bond we have.
When I see you stalking him all day, it just makes me feel sorry for him.
The love I feel.
That is super duper naughty, you dirty girl!
Spill!
Fisher of Condemnation!
Direct damage!
I'm not wrong.
I can change it all.
No matter what it takes,
I won't let this world deny my feelings anymore!
In the end,
Kazuki will be mine!
Understood.
Crap!
Dude, you beat me!
Wow, you're so good, Kazuki!
Good?
He's the best!
Now it's my turn and you're going down.
No way I'm losing to you!
Hey, so can you take a look at my deck?
Sure thing!
Oh, you're going to use red?
Yep!
Because I think the gem theme signi is so cute!
Yuzuki thinks so, too.
You know, I'm a little thirsty.
Hey, um, if I get juice, can I bring it in here?
Oh, yeah, of course.
Kazuki, will you come with?
Huh?
Hey, wait!
What about-
No, over here!
Huh?
Sorry I had to trick you.
I just said the whole juice thing because I couldn't think of a better way to get you alone.
Do you think we could go out together?
Um, look.
I do like you, Honoka.
But just not in that way.
Sorry.
Because there's somebody else, right?
No, there's nobody else, I swear.
Are you sure?
What about Yuzuki?
It's not because of her.
You two are always together.
So you can't blame people for thinking it.
We all know!
Wait.
You all know what?
What are people thinking?
Duh, that you and Yuzuki are, like, doing stuff!
Everyone says you are.
You didn't know?
Who the hell is everyone?
I mean, that's so messed up!
Who'd even say that kind of sicko crap?
Tell me!
How could you think such a thing about Yuzuki?
Uh...
So who was it?
Tell me!
Matsumoto?
Or Senda?
Give me some names now!
I'll go set them straight!
Well, if the rumors aren't true, why are you so upset over what people say about you guys?
Drop it!
If I'm wrong about your weird relationship, then prove it!
Uh, prove it how?
Kiss me.
Huh?
Why do I have to do that?
Well, since I bared my soul to you,
the least you could do is give me a kiss!
If you're single and not doing something weird with your sister, what's the harm?
Am I right?
This is insane.
Uh...
No!
Kazuki, wait!
Something is definitely different.
Summon Cannon!
And with its effect, banish Lotus!
Ah!
I don't feel like I have a fever or anything,
but I'm burning up inside.
Is this a sign that maybe my wish...
It will come true.
At last.
Yuzuki, listen to me.
I'm going to ask one last time.
Yeah?
What is it?
You are correct.
If you do win this battle, your fondest wish will come true.
Are you sure about this?
When I saw what Hitoe became, I was mad that you kept me in the dark.
But still, even if you had told me what could happen right from the very beginning,
I would have wanted to keep on fighting.
I don't care what it might take.
I'll become an Eternal Girl at any cost.
Now attack with Eagle!
Go!
Right.
I've got to do this for my wish.
I feel really bad about what happened to Hitoe.
But...
Her wish was something that could come true without being a selector.
But mine?
There's nothing I can do.
People will always frown on it.
I need power.
I need a miracle!
Yuzuki.
Since you've made your decision,
let us join together for one final attack.
Now, the oath.
Do you remember it?
Yeah.
It's a…
I accept…
The Laws of the Selector.
I accept the Laws of the Selector.
And…
And upon this sacred oath, a new Eternal Girl shall be born!
A Domestere!
Is this…
It is the birth…
Of a new Eternal Girl.
What?
Wait…
What's happening?
Who cares?
It's your day off from school, Ruu!
Wouldn't you rather be playing your card game?
Nah…
I always have a good time with you no matter what we do.
And besides, we cross-battles might be fun, but after seeing all the pain they cause, I... I...
We can't be friends anymore.
What is it?
Nothing. Just trying to swallow a hiccup.
All right.
I have to stay away from those cars.
Hello?
Dude, why did you take off like that?
Onika's pretty ticked. She said you treated her like crap. You gotta apologize.
I'll help you smooth things over, but get back here, right?
Why are girls such drama queens?
Yuzuki's not like that.
She's always smiling.
And honest, too.
Even if she's upset, she tries to keep it to herself.
Duh! That you and Yuzuki are like doing stuff!
No, that's crazy.
Hey, I'm home.
Yuzuki? What happened?
Just got dizzy for a moment.
Sorry, I'll be fine.
Look, you better lie down.
Can you walk?
Thank you, Kazuki.
No problem.
Did you put something on?
What?
Like perfume?
You smell nice.
You know, they say if you like someone's natural smell, that person is the love of your life.
Huh?
I didn't come up with the idea. Just saying, that's all.
Come on, what are you talking about?
If you're trying to make me laugh, this is just kind of awkward.
Even if you like your family, the love of your life is someone else.
And if I was someone else?
Other than my twin?
We were born as two halves of one whole, so in order for us to be complete, maybe we just need to be together.
Something's not right.
With who?
You, my friends.
Did someone say something to you?
You can talk to me about anything, all right?
Kazuki, I'm yours if you need me.
Now and forever.
Can I come in?
Hitoi, did you eat, dear?
No, not even the lunch I brought you?
Sweetie, you have to eat something.
Oh, before I forget, I got a little gift for you.
Take a look.
You like this game, don't you?
I saw an ad about a new WeCross deck being released, so I thought I'd get you one to cheer you up.
Why don't you flip through it and see what you got?
Oh, I bought a cake also.
Tell you what, I'm gonna bring up a big ol' slice for you, okay?
Be right back.
Be back.
Ah!
Ah.
Oh, God.
To be gone now, we installed aお!
No, no, no.
Here we go.
Why not wait?
Nice to meet you, Selector.
終わりのドアが開き始まる闇 危うい答えそこに見え隠れる 今日の祈りは明日多分になる
天と地を映す 逆園の迷路 回り出した 歯車
人ごみの中で 耳を澄ましたら 魂を招く あの鈴の音 響く空へ
無限の果てまでも 進むしかない 自分で選んだ 未来だから
届かない今すぐも 揺れる陽炎を いつか取り戻す 笑顔の場所
次回の動画でお会いしましょう